-嘿  -你可算来了
-Hey! -There you are.
到底是什么重要的事不能发短信说的
So what's the big news and why didn't you just text me?
因为我想看到在我告诉你后
Because I wanted to see the expression on your face
你脸上的吃惊表情  好了  我要说了
When I told you-- okay, here goes:
那位超帅气的学长乔希
So that really hot senior Josh
邀请我这周参加他的派对
Invited me to his party this weekend.
还说了可以带个同伴
And he said I could bring a friend.
快告诉俺整件事的来龙去脉
So tell me how it all went down.
好的  好的  好的
Okay okay okay.
当乔希问我时  我正站在储物柜前
So I was standing at my locker when Josh asked me.
我当时太紧张了  就把我的头发掩在柜子里了
I got so nervous I closed my hair in the door
然后我只能这么站着
And I had to stand there like this.
别急着高兴
Wait a minute.
咱们的老妈从来不让咱俩参加高年级派对
Our moms will never let us go to a senior party.
-我有解决之道  -噢  看来只能撒谎了
-Already solved that. -Ooh, we're gonna lie.
谁说要撒谎了  你那撒谎的伎俩能骗得过谁啊
We can't. You're a terrible liar.
别小瞧俺
I am not.
我说的事实
Yeah you are.
每次你撒谎的时候  音调就会变高
Whenever you lie, your voice gets really high.
谁说的
huh-uh!
好了  以下是本次行动的计划
Okay, so here's the plan.
你知道有个能拨出假电话的应用程序吧
You know that app that lets you create fake phone calls?
能拨出什么的什么
That what that creates what?
有个手机软件  可以拨出假的电话号码
There's a phone app that you can create fake phone calls with.
我所要做的就是录下一些我妈所说的话
All I have to do is record my mom saying some stuff
这样听起来就像是她允许我去参加派对了
That sounds like she's giving me permission to go to the party.
这样啊  当俺娘听到时
Ah, then when my mom hears it
-她就会让我去  -总算开窍了
-She'll let me go. -Exactly.
接下来就是乔希和我坠入爱河了
And we go to the party and Josh falls in love with me.
没错  他的帅气伙伴也会和我坠入爱河
Oh, and his cute best friend falls in love with me,
但我会告诉他  我名花有主了
But I tell him that I have a boyfriend,
而他却拿俺没办法了
But he doesn't take no for an answer--
-说够了吗  -再然后
-Are you done? -And then
又有第三个帅哥对我感兴趣...
There's a third guy that gets interested...
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
■
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z  cxqdcc
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
■
校订： line
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第四集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E04  Appy Days
噢  查莉啊
Oh, Charlie.
你知道爸爸是爱你的
You know daddy loves you,
但是爸爸已经和娃娃玩了快一百次了
But daddy's played baby about 100 times
而且爸爸感觉不太舒服  想休息一下
And he doesn't feel so good. He needs to rest.
噢  好吧  好吧
Oh, okay. All right.
噢  有了  咱们来玩
Oh, I know! Let's play
娃娃看爸爸睡觉觉
Baby watches daddy take a nap.
啊  孩子们  我需要你们的救援
Aha! Boys, I need your help.
-说真的  -今天我被蜘蛛咬了一口
-Really? -Today at work I got bit by a spider.
你不就是个灭虫的吗  这不常有的事吗
You're an exterminator. Doesn't that happen every day?
不幸的是  碰巧让一种我过敏的蜘蛛给咬了
Well, this particular spider I happen to be mildly allergic to.
恶心死了
That's disgusting!
快盖上  快盖上  我觉着我快吐了
<i>Cover it, cover it, cover it.</i> <i>Please, I think I'm gonna barf.</i>
谢谢你们的关心
Thank you so much for your concern.
我去看过医生了
I went and I saw the doctor.
她说过几天就可以消肿了
She says the swelling's going to be gone in a couple of days.
噢  真是令人发指
Oh, that's revolting.
不过这的确让你的肚子看起来小多了
Although it does make your tummy look smaller.
“天啊  爸爸  我该如何帮你呢”
"gosh, dad, how could I help?"
谢谢你们这样问
thanks for asking.
PJ我需要你明天替我上天班
P.J., I need you to cover for me at work tomorrow.
我这里已经忙得不可开交了
I got a really busy day.
好吧  我去就是了
Fine, I'll help.
但我可不想也弄只巨型手臂
But I better not get a giant arm too.
我还是多买几件T恤吧
I just bought some shirts.
盖比  我去上楼休息了
Gabe, I gotta go upstairs and rest,
我需要你照顾查莉  明白了吗
So I need you to look after Charlie, okay?
我该怎么照顾查莉
What am I supposed to do with Charlie?
你和她玩娃娃
Wha-- you play baby with her.
拜托了  她好这口
Come on, she loves it.
快去捡
Fetch.
好了  艾薇  我要准备实施骗老妈计划了
Okay, Ivy, I'm about to launch phase one of operation fool mom.
啥  听着  我还不知道
What?  No. I don't know what
我要在派对上穿什么  咱们先实施计划成吗
I'm gonna wear to the party. Let's trick our moms first.
-嗨  老妈  -嘿
-Hi mom. -Hey.
什么  老妈
What?  Mom,
我可是一天没见到您了  而我却只得到了一声嘿
I haven't seen you all day and all I get is a hey?
我的错  嗨  泰迪
Sorry. Hi, Teddy!
老妈  能帮我把这线头从我毛衣上拽掉吗
Uh, mom, could you get this loose thread on my sweater?
-在哪  -噢  应该是已经掉了
-Where is it? -Oh, must have fallen off.
线头
Threads.
没想到吧
Go figure.
你没事吧
How are you doing?
没事啊  对了  老妈
Fine. Oh, mom,
能问你个私人问题吗
Could I ask you a personal question?
宝贝  当然了
Honey, of course you can.
太好了
Great.
到底什么  什么问题啊
What's-- what's-- what's the question?
噢  我还没想好
Oh, I don't have one right now.
只是...
Just...
先为以后铺好路
You know, good to know for down the road.
说真的  你没事吧
Seriously, how are you doing?
噢  老妈  你懂西班牙语是吧
Oh, mom, you took Spanish, right?
那这句话什么意思
What does this mean?
意思是我喜欢那个男孩  他人很好
That means I like that boy. He's very nice.
等一下  你不是选法语的吗
Wait a minute, I thought you were taking french.
噢  没错
Oh, wow.
我说我怎么看不懂呢
Guess that's why I didn't understand it.
-我爱你  老妈  -我也爱你  宝贝
-I love you, mom. -I love you too, honey.
怪了  通常这种对话只会出现在PJ身上
Weird-- I usually have those conversations with P.J.
老爸  快让它停下来吧
Dad, make it stop.
-让什么停下来  -来玩娃娃
-Make what stop? -Play baby.
那个
That.
我走到哪  她说到哪“玩娃娃
Everywhere I go there she is "play baby,
玩娃娃  玩娃娃”
Play baby, play baby."
抱歉了  儿子  但你总算讨某人喜欢了
I'm sorry, son, but somebody has finally found you likeable.
不管了  我受不了了
Well, I can't take it anymore.
我这就去图书馆
I'm going to the library.
-图书馆  -没错  老爸
-The library? -Yeah, dad.
你没有听错
It's come to that.
-你知道图书馆在哪吗  -我会找到的
-Do you even know where the library is? -I'll find it.
她来了
She's coming!
好了  你准备好电话了吗
Okay, are you ready with your phone?
一切就绪
Ready.
-噢  嗨  温茨太太  -嗨  泰迪
-Oh, hi, Mrs. Wentz. -Hi, Teddy.
-艾薇  你刚才听见我了吗  -没有啊
-Ivy, didn't you hear me? -No.
我刚才边按喇叭边喊你“艾薇”十分钟了
I have been honking and screaming "ivy" for 10 minutes.
那是你啊
That was you?
我在这里可是颇有名气的
I know so many people.
-赶紧走吧  -先别急  我想先问个问题
-Let's go. -Before that, quick question.
-什么问题  -有位学长叫乔希
-What? -There's a senior boy named Josh
然后他要请俺俩去参加他的派对  俺能去吗
And he invited Teddy and me to a party this weekend. Can I go?
听着  艾薇  你知道我在这方面对你的政策
Now, Ivy, you know my policy.
除非我见过那个男孩  不然就死了这条心吧
Unless I've met the boy, the answer's no.
我也很确信泰迪的妈妈也是这么说的
And I'm sure Teddy's mom said the same thing.
噢  其实我还没问我妈妈呢
Oh well, actually I haven't asked my mom yet.
噢对了  为什么我不现在给她打电话来问问
Oh hey, why don't I call my mom at work and see what she says?
通了
It's ringing.
-嗨  老妈  -嗨泰迪
-Hi, mom. -<i>Hi, Teddy.</i>
老妈  我想问下我能去参加派对吗
Uh, mom, I was calling to see if I can go to a party?
-在哪  -就在我朋友乔希家
-<i>Where is it?</i> -It's at my friend Josh's house.
你知道乔希吧
You know Josh, right?
我喜欢那个男孩  他人很好
<i>I like that boy.</i> <i>He's very nice.</i>
这么说来  我能去参加吗
So what do you say? Can I go to the party?
宝贝  当然了
<i>Honey, of course you can.</i>
谢了  老妈  世上只有妈妈好
Thanks, mom. You're the best.
好了  不打扰您了  爱你
All right, I don't want to keep you. Love you!
我也爱你  宝贝
<i>Love you too, honey.</i>
看
See?
泰迪可以去了
Teddy gets to go.
这个嘛  既然艾米都同意了
Well, if it's okay with Amy.
我就没什么问题了  你也可以去了
It's okay with me. You can go.
谢了  老妈  世上只有妈妈好
Thanks, mom. You're the best.
我喜欢那个男孩  他人很好
<i>I like that boy.</i> <i>He's very nice.</i>
什么声
What was that?
噢  我在模仿我老妈
Oh, I was just doing an impression of my mom.
我也经常模仿我老爸
I also do my dad.
“泰迪  你给我进来”
"Teddy, get in here!"
什么事  老爸
What is it, dad?
“谁把最后一个甜甜圈给吃了”
"who ate the last donut?"
是你自己  老爸
You did, dad.
好了  我们还是先走了
well, we'd better get going.
嗯  什么这么香啊
Mmm, what smells so good?
-热狗  -噢
-Hot dogs. -Oh.
艾米·邓肯做的热狗天下无敌
Nothing makes boiled water smell better
遗臭万年
Than Amy Duncan's hot dogs.
应该是在褒我
This should be good.
老妈
Um, so, mom,
我问下我能去乔希家开的派对吗
I was wondering if I could go to a party at Josh's house.
他是超级帅的学长  但您不认识他
He's this really cute senior. You don't know him.
对不起了  泰迪  死了这条心吧
I'm sorry, Teddy, the answer's no.
你知道我在这方面对你的政策
You know my policy.
噢  别这样啊  艾薇的妈妈都同意让她去了
Oh, come on! Ivy's mom is letting her go.
-玛丽·卢·温茨同意了  -是的
-Mary Lou wentz gave permission? -Yes.
没错  她同意了
Yes, she did.
如果你想证实下  我可以给她打电话
And I can call her if you want to hear from her.
打啊
I'd love to.
嗨  温茨太太  我是泰迪·邓肯
Hi, Mrs. Wentz, it's Teddy Duncan.
等我打开免提  好吗
I'm gonna put you on speaker, okay?
听说您同意艾薇去参加派对了  是吗
So, Mrs. Wentz, you're letting Ivy go to that party, right?
我同意了
<i>It's okay with me.</i>
真的吗  玛丽·卢  因为...
Are you sure, Mary Lou, because--
我同意了
<i>it's okay with me.</i>
是吗  难道你就没有半点...
Really, you're not the least bit--
我同意了
<i>it's okay with me.</i>
坏了  断线了
Oops, lost her.
我能去了吗
So can I go to the party?
这个嘛
Well...
既然玛丽·卢都同意了  我也没什么意见了
If it's okay with Mary Lou, it's okay with me.
噢  谢谢了  老妈  我太爱您了
Ooh, thank you, mommy! Love you so much.
是啊...谁不爱有求必应的老妈啊
Yeah... No one loves mom more than when she's saying yes.
电话有些不对劲
That was an interesting phone call.
是吗
Was it?
是的
Yeah.
肯定有问题
Yeah, it was.
还不错吧
Having fun yet, kid?
不  弗恩  一点都不好
No, vern, I am not.
这是你第一次匍匐前行吗
First time in a crawl space?
我真不敢相信我老爸竟然靠做这个维持生计
I can't believe my dad does this for a living.
看来我真应该
I'm really gonna have to start
好好学习了
paying attention in school.
嘘
Shh!
啊噢  老鼠
Uh-oh, rats.
老鼠
Rats?
我以为我们在抓负鼠
I thought we were catching possums.
有时候这由不得我们
Sometimes the critters make the decisions.
-老鼠在哪里  -就在我们身边
- Where are the rats? - All around us.
有几十只
dozens.
也许几百只
Maybe hundreds.
轻点  如果它们受到惊吓
Quiet. If they smell fear,
我们会死的很惨的
We're both dead.
真是命悬一线啊
That was horrifying.
把盐给我  孩子
Pass the salt, kid.
呃  这是杀虫剂
Uh, that's termite poison.
你只有一次机会把它们放在三明治上
You only put that on a sandwich once.
我的错  真对不起啊
Whoops. Sorry.
今天终于见到你本人了
Well, it's nice to finally meet you.
你爸老和我谈起你
Your dad sure talks about you a lot.
-真的  -一直在说
-He does? -All the time.
说你怎么怎么聪明
Goes on and on about you-- how you're smart,
怎么怎么努力  怎么怎么受欢迎
Driven, popular.
-他真这样说我的  -是啊
-He said all that about me? -Oh yeah.
他很骄傲
He's very proud.
好了  该工作了  泰德
Well, lunch break's over, Ted.
泰德  泰德
Ted? Ted?!
噢  泰迪是我的姐姐
Oh, Teddy's my sister.
噢  那你一定是那个很有自信
Oh, then you must be the self-confident
聪明伶俐  爱恶作剧的那个孩子吧
Sharp-as-a-tack mischief-maker.
那是盖比
That's Gabe.
嗯
Hmm.
那你一定是刚摆脱尿布的小可爱
You're the little cutie pie who just got out of diapers?
我是家里的老大
I'm the oldest!
-PJ  -噢  没错
- P.J.? - Oh right, of course.
PJ  你是个好人
P.J.-- You're the nice one.
就这个
That's it?
别人都是顶呱呱的
Everyone else is sharp,
聪明的和可爱的
Smart and adorable
而我只是好
And I'm just nice?
我知道如何让你重新喜笑颜开
I know what'll turn that frown upside down.
去搬那老鼠袋子
You get to carry the rat bag.
-嗨  艾米  -嗨  玛丽·卢  快进来
-Hi, Amy. -Hi, Mary Lou! Come on in.
-好的  -什么风把你吹来了
- Okay. - What brings you here?
（注：boa既有围脖的意思，也有蟒蛇的意思）
艾薇忘带围脖了
Ivy forgot her boa.
现在她去派对了  她需要她的蟒蛇
Now if she's going to a party, she needs her boa.
她们刚走  但别担心
They just left, but don't worry--
豹纹连衣裙会为她们增色不少的
The leopard-print dress will be festive enough.
艾米  我不得不说  我有些惊讶
I gotta say, Amy, I was a bit surprised
你居然为派对这事给泰迪亮了绿灯
You gave Teddy permission to go to that party.
我之所以给她亮绿灯
Well, I only said yes to Teddy
是因为你先给艾薇亮的绿灯
because you gave Ivy permission first.
在为人母这方面我还是很敬仰您的  来点饼干
You know how much I respect you as a mother. Cracker?
噢  谢谢了
Oh, thank you.
但是你先同意泰迪参加派对
But you gave Teddy permission first
然后我也同意了  因为我很敬仰您的
And I said yes because of how much I respect you.
好的  成了  成了  你们都是好妈妈
Okay, yeah yeah yeah, best moms ever.
没看见我正看动画片呢吗
I'm trying to watch my cartoons here.
我  我并不是先同意泰迪参加派对的
I-- I didn't give Teddy permission first.
但是我听到泰迪给你打的电话了
But I heard Teddy call you at work.
不  泰迪从没在我工作的时候打电话给我过  我很费解啊
No, Teddy never called me at work. I'm confused.
-对  我也是  -还是让我来点拨你们下吧
-Yeah, me too. -May I enlighten you?
-快点  -这两个女孩用了一个手机程序
-Spill it. -The girls used a phone app to make it sound like
让它听起来像是你们俩同意了她们去派对这事
You each gave them permission to go to the party.
-什么  -她们不是的
-What? -They didn't!
噢  玛丽·卢  别太天真了
Oh, Mary Lou, but they did.
所以  妈妈  如果我下一次捅了什么娄子
Now, mom, so next time I'm bad--
当然我们都知道那是迟早的事
we both know there will be a next time--
不要忘了今天我为你们做了什么
Just remember this moment when I did something for you.
等她们回家看我怎么收拾她们
They are gonna be in so much trouble when they get home.
为什么我们要等她们回家
Why wait till they get home?
又不是只有她们知道有手机程序
They're not the only ones who know about apps.
对  没错
No, they aren't.
可是我们知道什么手机程序
What do we know about apps?
我这个手机有GPS功能
I have a g.P.S. App on this phone.
就是说我可以追踪艾薇的手机
That means I can track Ivy's phone.
我们可以去派对了吗
Shall we go to a party?
我很乐意
I'd be "appy" to.
你好
hello?
亲爱的泰迪  我是盖比
Teddy dear, Gabe here.
在我向你透露这些消息之前
Before I share the news,
当我需要帮助的时候  请铭记这一刻
let's remember this moment the next time I need a favor.
为什么你每次打电话都要以毛骨悚然的问题开场呢
Why do all of your calls start with the same creepy question?
老妈和玛丽·卢太太知道了你们的小阴谋
Mom and Mrs. Wentz know all about the phony phone calls.
什么  她们怎么知道的
What?! How'd they find out?
这仍是一个谜  不管是谁...
That part remains a mystery. Anywho...
她们正用GPS追踪你们  现在就在路上呢
They're tracking you on g.P.S. And heading your way.
什么  妈妈们用GPS追踪我们
What?  Our moms are tracking us on g.P.S.
GPS  她们不应该知道这个的
G.P.S.? They're not supposed to know about that.
天啊  谢谢你了  盖比  我欠你一个人情
Oh gosh, thanks, Gabe. I owe you one.
算你说对了
So it would seem.
你在这啊  我想查莉想和你玩娃娃了
There you are. I think Charlie wants to play baby with you.
她一直在说  “盖比  盖比”
She keeps going, "gabe, Gabe!"
她爱怎么说就怎么说  反正我不去
She can say it all she wants. It's not gonna happen.
我已经对她和她那傻缺娃娃厌烦了
I'm sick of her and I'm sick of that stupid doll.
噢  查莉  不要这样  我不是那个意思
Oh, Charlie, come on! I didn't mean it.
我只是在做盖比该做的事啊
I was just Gabe being Gabe.
嘿  你回来了  今天还顺利吗
Hey, there he is! How'd it go today?
我今天的亮点是
the highlight of my day
搬了一袋子的老鼠
Was carrying a bag of rats.
弗恩肯定会很赞赏你的
Vern must like you
因为他对搬老鼠袋的人选可是很讲究的
because he's awful particular about his rat bag.
弗恩告诉了我  你是怎么说我们的
Vern told me what you said about us kids.
-我怎么说的  -别的孩子的评价都很高很高
-What'd I say? -That everyone else is so great
而我只是好而已
And I'm just nice.
那又怎么了
So?
你挺好的  有什么问题吗
You're nice, what's wrong with that?
“好”是你朋友用来形容
So "nice" is what your friend calls the ugly girl
你想约出去的丑姑娘的
He wants you to go out with.
我在你眼里就是这样的人
Is that all I am to you--
仅仅是个丑姑娘吗
An ugly girl?
噢  这真是太刺激了
Oh, this is so exciting--
去缉拿那两个小骗子
Going after the perps.
等一下  女孩们掉头了
Wait, the girls are turning around.
-什么  -好像她们要掉头回你家了
- What? - Looks like they're headed back to your house.
抓紧你的包包  玛丽·卢  看我的漂移大法
Hold on your your purse, Mary Lou. We're making a u-ey.
爽啊
Oh yeah!
-你知道什么更爽吗  -什么
- You know what would be great? - <i>What?</i>
如果我们有一个警笛和警灯
If we had a siren and a flashing light.
什么手机程序都有
They got app for everything.
嘿
Hey.
-我想我们需要谈一谈  -我没有心情
-I think we gotta talk. -I'm not in the mood.
噢  我这么对你说话可不好哦
Oh, that wasn't very nice.
噢  别这样  我说你好是对你的称赞
Oh come on. When I said you were nice that was a compliment.
你最多只能用这个词来称赞我吗
That was the best thing you could say about me?
这简单的一个词意味深长啊
I think that says a lot.
听着  儿子
Look, P.J.,
作为一个父亲对我来说最重要的
As a father, the most important thing to me
是我的孩子们都是品行端正
Is that my kids are good people--
善良体贴  关心他人
Kind-hearted, genuinely concerned about other people...
的好人
Nice.
嘿  要是论这个标准来说你可是最令老爸骄傲的孩子
Hey, by that standard you're the kid I'm most proud of.
-真的  -真的
-Really? -Really.
谢谢了  老爸
Thanks, dad.
嘿  谢谢你今天帮我代班
Hey, thank you for helping me out on the job today.
呃  你知道的  我倒是
Uh, you know, I was kinda
希望有一天这个可以
Hoping maybe someday we could
持续进行下去
Make that a permanent thing.
“邓肯和儿子”
"Duncan & son."
噢
Oh!
这倒提醒我了  哥要去学习了
That reminds me-- better hit those books.
这个可一点都不好
Well, that wasn't nice at all.
噢  你们两个在这里干吗  派对提早结束了吗
Oh, what are you two doing here? Did the party end early?
没  我们还是决定不去了
No, we decided not to go.
事实上
The truth is
我们为了让你们同意我们去派对欺骗了你
We tricked you into giving us permission to go to the party.
你真知道吗
Did you now?
是的  我们为自己的所做所为而感到羞愧
Yes, I'm ashamed to say we did.
在去派对的路上有些东西让我们改变了主意
But on the way there something made us change our minds.
是什么东西
And what's that?
我们看到了葡萄汁的广告牌
We saw the grape juice billboard.
就是一位小女孩和母亲亲切拥抱
You know the one where the girl is hugging her mom
因为她很喜欢葡萄汁
Because she's so happy with the juice?
“葡萄妈妈们所见略同”  我有点熟啊
"grape moms think alike," I'm familiar with it.
总之  那让我们想到了你们俩是多么的好
Anyway that got us to thinking about how wonderful you two are
然后我们聊了聊
And we talked it over
并一致认为你们的女儿应该要做对得起你们的事
and agreed that you deserved better
最后我们就不去了
And decided not to go.
这全是真话
It's true.
总之  我们知道我们的所作所为也许会受到惩罚
Anyway, we know you're probably gonna punish us,
我们没有怨言
But we're okay with that.
那么  我们等下再讨论这个
Well, we can talk about that later.
我很骄傲你们能向我们坦白从宽
I'm really proud that you guys told us the truth.
我也是
I am too.
世上只有妈妈好
Darn you for raising us so well.
那还用说
It's what I do.
嘿  艾薇  我要来了  你到了吗
Hey, Ivy, I'm on my way out. Are you here?
我就在你家门口
I'm right in front of your house.
你确定我们现在去不晚吗
Are you sure it's not too late to go?
噢  傻瓜  这种派对是通宵的
Oh, girlfriend, these senior parties go all night.
-打算去哪啊  -去床上
-Going somewhere? -Back to bed.
知道就好
You got that right.
被我妈逮到了  去不了了
Caught by mom. Can't go.
-如果你不去  那我也不去了  -知道就好
-If you're not going, I'm not going. -You got that right.
嗨  查莉
Hi, Charlie.
查莉  别这样
Charlie, come on.
你要我说多少次对不起啊
How many times do I have to say I'm sorry?
要我怎么样你才能原谅我
What is it gonna take for you to forgive me?
你宝宝
You baby.
“你宝宝”
"you baby"?
什么意思
What does that mean?
好吧  查莉  我不知道你使了什么招让他当娃娃
Well, Charlie, I don't know how you got him to do that,
但是谢谢你了  这够我们乐几年了
But thank you. We'll be enjoying this for years.
祝你好运咯  小查莉
now say good luck, Charlie.
你想让我吐你一身吗  我可不怕
Do you want me to spit up? 'cause I'm not afraid to go there.
犟孩子
Cranky baby.
嘿  大家还好吧  听着  听着
Hey, how's it going? Good good.
还记得几周前我提到的
Remember a few weeks ago I mentioned something about
要帮我一个忙吗
Cashing in my favors?
现在机会来了  你们就说从来没看到过我
Well, today's the day. You two never saw me.
再见
Bye-bye now.
请进
come in.
那小子在楼上
He's upstairs, boys.
-为什么你不帮他  老妈  -他今天没洗碗
-Why'd you give him up, mom? -He didn't do the dishes.
千万别惹老娘我
Don't cross mama.